Hello friends,
you are very welcome to our YouTube channel,
in this Ashish video we will talk about the
advisor job of ICICI Prudential Life Insurance,
one of it
is entry and the other is adventure, you are
telling here in front of you that these are employees, these are
regular employees, they
work as department employees, but
I have made a video about this also, you
can come to the channel and see
how to apply, the answer to this is roles
which is folded, okay friends, today
we will talk about adventure,
about Punjab, friends, because if this
job is seen according to me, if
both are seen by doing competition, then advisor job is the
best, for those people who
cannot handle pressure,
advisor job will be very good,
so now let us talk about this
in detail, secondly let me tell you that this
job, friends, if you have passed 10th, then
this job is yours, minimum
qualification for this you need two
hands, so if you have a complete  After watching this video, there is
no need for any qualifier or actress here and friends,
before moving ahead, I request you that if you have
not yet subscribed to this channel, then do
subscribe from here so
that whatever other
banking jobs or private banking jobs come in the future, and
you get the notification of it
first, so friends, you should definitely
subscribe to this channel as well, on the other hand, you will get to know
that you are operating a banking job,
whether it is a bank or a
private bank or a government bank, so
our channel can be very helpful for you,
we keep bringing videos of banking jobs daily, so this
video, it may be that you may feel that it will take
some time, but
I will try to tell you in detail
how you can apply for this resolution
and if there are all other careers, then the first thing to
talk about is see, it is written here that the direct
benefit of becoming and adventurous jobs, if you
become a judge, then what are the
benefits you are going to get, here
unlimited earning potential, so we have seen
that the employee  The salary of the theorem employee who is a
designer is tree
but according to the wish but here you will have
unlimited income, the more work you do, the
more money you will get, okay, apart from this,
friends, you will also get rewards and tech
medicine here, so this
cream can also be there, revised examination
and this action can also be there, as far as I have
seen, there is revolt and recommendation for pride quota,
where awards are also given, medals are also
given, okay and you
also get a lot of encouragement there, friends, if we
talk about career progression here, then
friends, the career
progression here is very good,
friends, if you do this fresh celery,
suppose you have passed the given button, okay and there is
pressure and your age is more than 18 years, then
you should take it here knowingly and
give it slowly, friends,
if your performance here is good, then you will definitely
become a family member of ICC Pressure Life Insurance and friends,
you will also be made a team leader there
and where you have no work, whatever is there  There will be people
below you,
you have to train them for one or two hours daily, you have to
explain a little about all the insurance plans,
it is not very easy and
in the beginning friends you will have to work a little hard,
after that friends your life is going to be very
easy, there is more
convenience here, see what does more convenience mean,
you will work as an advisor, so the
way of working there is
very good in SSC, friends I am
saying this because I have experienced this in front of my
eyes,
here you will have to sell the
insurance, you
can sell it only through a tablet, that is, if
you have a smartphone or a tablet, then
all the case
applications of ICC Chief Insurance, Pretshila Beans will be given in your tablet,
you have to go to every customer and
whatever plan you want to sell after going to the customer, it will be
on your tablet, now you have to see it and tell the customer,
just run it, you have to convince the customer a
lot  You have here, okay, this has
another benefit that you will be
able to sell more plans here, this will give a lot more
value to your customer because the more we will be able to
sell, the more you will be able to show to the
customer, so the customer will have trust on the
paper, but yes, whatever this
temple is telling is absolutely correct
and we can buy plain water from this, so
suppose you are
not able to sell any plan, then
you are also given support here, okay, you
get tanning, along with that you also get development
and major support, you
also get service support, you will get
support from your team members, if the team
member, suppose he is busy with some work and is
not picking up your call, then
you can also get information about this from the PCC member,
you
can also get some information from there as an emergency,
now let's talk friends, how to do it,
okay, so see here, to
do it simply, there is an airplane mode
button, you have to click on it,
its link is also  I will give it to you, if
you click on it,
this page will open in front of you. It is written here
that the qualifications required to be there is a
dangerous life insurance
advisor. So, whatever you need to do here, this
call vacation, what will you do, it is
written here
according to the Insurance Act 1938, recently
dismissed IRDA I in 2016, so those candidates who have
passed the relations in 2016, they should be
worried about it and it is important to pass the time. Along with
this, friends, you have to
write down the IRDA I, so it is necessary to solve this problem, how did you get it,
how
can you fly the admin test, secondly, here the
company documentation, here you will have to
submit all the documents, what to do,
that too I will tell you, it is in the second step,
friends, after submitting the documents,
you will have to appear for an interview, you will have to enter for this qualification
and as you enter the training password,
after that for the same training
Related to that, you will have to appear for an additional
government exam, which
you will have to answer if you pass the exam, then
after that you will get a
judge of this court, a code, this is the main one
because through the court you
can do this business, let us understand it
in simple steps how you can become an entrepreneur, first of all
friends,
how will this represent you, you will get this most important, so mail
it to the mail here in
which you come to the mail and in the beginning you can put your
password and send it to them, after receiving this
mail, along with
this proof, your Aadhar card as
address proof, dispute as
your powers, you can take the
marksheet of 1012 graduation as an addition proof,
PAN card is necessary,
without PAN card it will not work,
after that you will see your passport size photo, after
seeing this you can forward it to this email,
so I told you that you do not have it,
you are in other states, I have
forwarded it to this email, okay, money and I will forward it to
you, so near
Whichever advisor I am, he will contact you
and after that whatever hard copy is there, you can take it from
you,
you can also go to their office and submit it, okay,
only after submitting it, I will tell you again
that your document is complete,
after that your training will start,
after the training is over, there will be an exam, which is the
IATA exam,
through which friends you
get a quota, okay, and
after taking the quota, friends, you will have a potential
interview and after that you
can start your work, whether you are fine at home
or you have to
go to the office and work or
go to the market and do this work, or suppose you have an
appointment with a customer on a phone call, you have to go and
work there, even if you do not work, no
one will put pressure on you, if you work
then everyone else will be
different from you, okay, you will fit me,
but secondly, definitely apply here, the one
who has got 925 jobs, there is nothing like this here in it,
Monday to  You
can work anytime on Sunday and
you can also earn a good income here, number two
salary, rest of the gyms play, you will
get messages from that too, till you do
good work, salary, okay, if you do
not work there also then after two months they will
fire you with less, yes, here also
you will work as advance and if you do this work then
you will get this commission for that update, if you do
not do this work then you will
not get anything, it will remain with the clutch only and if
you need any information related to this then
you can tell us through comment below,
so please
like, share and give complaint about the journey which is not in this video for a penny